I want to look at the sensible sky this
我想 看看这明智的天空
is cool because we think about smart
很酷，因为 我们考虑聪明
devices we think about the ability to
我们考虑的设备能力
you know I have a nest thermostat at my
你知道我有一个巢温控器
house okay that means I save money by
房子好 ，这意味着我省钱 的
running a thermostat that intelligently
运行一个智能的恒温器
figures out when I'm home turns off the
当我在家时关掉它
AC air the heat at that time and then
AC 空气中的热量 ，在那个时候，然后
when I get home it turns it back on or
当我回到家时，它会重新打开 或
if I'm if I'm making the trip home if
如果我是的，如果我要回家的话
I'm leaving work and I know that the
我要离开工作，我知道
house is a little bit cold because I can
房子有点冷，因为我可以
bring up the app I can turn on the heat
调出应用程序，我可以打开 热
from my app and then by the time I get
从我的应用程序 ，然后到 我得到
home it's nice and cozy
家里很好，很舒适
so sensibo sky takes it kind of to
因此，敏感天空对它有所帮助
another level because of course nest
另一个层次 因为 当然是 窝
and smart thermostats like nest they
和他们 一样的智能恒温器
require a hardwired central air
需要一个硬连线的中央空气
conditioning unit furnace those kinds of
调节装置炉那些种类
things it's a hard wired connection
事情是有线 连接
sensibo is completely different you want
sensibo是你想要的完全不同
to know so you picture an AC unit that's
知道 所以你想象一个AC单位
in your window or like a you know if
在你的窗口或像你知道如果
you've got a heat exchanger you know
你知道，你有一台换热器
there all kinds of devices that you
你有各种各样的设备
might use but I think in particular of
可能会使用但我 特别想到
you know the wall hanging AC units not
你知道壁挂式交流单元 不是
central air but AC units that use a
中央空调，但AC单位使用
remote control yeah right you use a
遥控器 对，没错，你使用
remote control to adjust the temperature
遥控 调节温度
my AC back in the apartment before we
在 我们 之前 我的AC回到了 公寓
got central air at the house it had had
在它所拥有的房子里有空气
a remote control it was just in the
它只是一个遥控器
window right it was a great little unit
窗口对，这是一个很棒的小单位
but you had to be home to adjust it and
但你必须回家调整它
there was no intelligence to it
它没有 智慧
whatsoever
任何
so what sensibo does is it's an app
所以sensibo做的是它是一个应用程序
connected device through your Wi-Fi and
通过Wi-Fi连接设备
it then allows you to control your AC
它然后允许您 控制您的AC
unit that has infrared remote control
具有红外遥控功能的单元
technology you can control it from your
技术，你可以从 你的 控制
app okay okay so you think about an AC
应用没关系， 所以你想一个AC
unit that has a remote control as long
单元，其具有遥控只要
as it has an infrared remote control
因为它有一个红外遥控器
sensibo sky is going to be able to
sensibo 天空 将能够
control it so let's get into the box and
控制它，让我们 进入 框中
actually get a look at what this what
实际上看看这是什么
this device looks like so here we are
这个装置看起来像我们这样
this is the box for sensibo sky
这是 sensibo天空 的盒子
and nice little device let's just get
和漂亮的小设备让我们得到
right into it it's it's so super simple
对它 来说它是如此超级简单
I mean here's our step-by-step
我的意思是这是我们的一步一步
instructions download and install the
说明下载 并安装
app follow the instructions in the app
应用程序按照应用程序的说明
enjoy and keep cool
享受并保持冷静
those are your instructions would simple
那些是你的指示很简单
simple so there it is that's the
这很简单所以就是这样
sensible sky as you can see let's get
明智的 天空，你可以看到让我们得到
some of this wrapper off of here
这里有一些包装
there we go I'll just stick that over
我们走我就坚持， 超过
there and we've got a little bit of a
还有，我们已经得到 的 一点点
kind of a like a double sided tape kind
那种像一个双面胶种
of thing going on over here so I can
在这里发生的事情，所以我可以
just stick it to the wall
把它贴在墙上
it's also got a mount that I can screw
它也有一个我可以拧的座位
it in to the wall and then here we've
它在 墙上 ，然后我们在这里
got USB micro input and what looks like
有USB微输入和看起来像
some kind of a data port I'm not I'm not
某种数据端口我不是我不是
sure on that one it almost seems like
请务必在一个 几乎好像
it's maybe a connection for a connected
它可能是连接的连接
furnace or some I don't know what that
炉或 一些我不知道那是什么
is we'll look it up you can look that up
是 我们来看看 它 ，你可以看看 ，最多
as well I don't think that that's gonna
我也不认为 那会那样
affect our use of it today might be for
影响我们今天使用它 可能是为了
firmware updates and things like that as
固件更新和 类似的 事情
well further in the box how simple is
以及进一步在 框中 是 多么的简单
that now it is sensible sky is powered
现在 是明智的天空是动力的
by USB micro as I mentioned there it's
通过USB micro，就像我在那里提到的那样
got just the USB micro jack so it comes
只有USB微型 插孔 所以它来了
with a what looks like a good long USB
看起来像一个很好的长USB
micro cable oh yeah oh there we go good
微电缆哦是啊哦，我们走得很好
length on that anyway so because it's
无论如何长度， 因为它是
USB micro it's gonna work anywhere in
USB micro它可以在任何地方工作
the world we don't need to have any
这个世界 我们不需要任何东西
fancy adapters we don't need to have any
花哨的适配器，我们不需要任何
anything that's you know extra special
你知道的任何特别的东西
to work overseas or anything like that
在海外工作或类似的事情
now it came with a little power brick
现在它配备了一个小 功率砖
here so that I can plug that in as well
在这里，我也可以插入它
the brick that it came with is it's one
它带来的砖就是它
amp so it doesn't need a lot of power
放大器所以它不需要很多 电力
most of the bricks that you already have
你已经拥有的大部分砖块
are going to have 2.4 amps or even
将有2.4安培或甚至
higher so this is you know this can be
更高，所以你知道 这可以
powered by basically any any little USB
基本上任何小USB供电
power cable that you have so I'm just
你有的 电源线 所以我只是
going to simply plug this in like the
简单地将其插入就像
instructions say so I'm just going to
指示说，所以我只是要
plug in the USB and we'll see what
插上USB，我们会看到什么
happens here if I can do this kind of
如果我能做到这一点 ， 就会发生 在这里
blindly there we go and now the sensible
盲目地我们走了，现在 明智了
logo is just kind of flash and blue
徽标只是一种闪光和蓝色
there on occasion so I'll just kind of
有时我会这样的
set that down there now I've got this
把它放在 那里我现在已经有了这个
really cool thing on my phone called
在我的手机上打电话真的很酷
miracast and it allows me to in fact
miracast ，它 实际上 允许我
bring up my phone on the screen for you
在屏幕上为你打开我的手机
so I can actually do that so how cool is
所以我 真的能这样做， 所以 有多酷
that so let's bring up the sensibo app
那就让我们提出一下 sensibo应用程序
there we are and back here so the first
我们在这里，所以第一个
thing that i need to do is select the
我需要做的是选择
sensible sky that's the device that i've
明智的天空，这是 我 的设备
purchased and it says connect your
购买它说连接你的
sensibo sky device to the power outlet
sensibo天空设备到电源插座
which i've done and then hit next now it
我已经 完成然后再打它了
says find the QR code located on the
说发现二维码位于
back of your sensible sky device and
你明智的天空设备背面
click next okay so on the back of my
点击下一个 没关系，所以在 我 的背面
device sure enough there it is it's itty
设备肯定 在那里它是它的 一切
bitty is my camera going to be able to
比特是我的相机能够做到的
read that let's see okay so now I can
阅读，让我们看到没问题，所以现在我可以
see the camera there let's see it's
看到相机 那里让我们看到它
choppy but let's see oh it actually did
波涛汹涌， 但让我们看看它确实 做到了
it Wow oh yeah choose an icon and name
哇哦，是的，选择一个图标和名字
the AC okay so I I'm gonna say this is
AC好吧所以 我要说这是
can we call this living room we're just
我们可以称这个客厅为 公正 吗？
we're basically pretending because we
我们基本上假装是因为我们
don't have an AC unit here at the studio
工作室里没有AC装置
that we can use with this so we're gonna
我们可以使用 这个，所以我们会
say living room next and I've left it as
接下来就说客厅 ，我就把它当成了
the default device allow sensible to
默认设备 允许合理
allow this to access this devices
允许此操作访问此设备
location all right in order to complete
位置 可以完成
the setup sensibo needs to get right
设置sensibo需要正确
settings permission the permission is
权限是设置权限
needed to check Wi-Fi and after setup is
需要检查Wi-Fi 和 设置 后
complete you may disable this permission
完成后，您可以禁用此权限
in settings apps configure settings
在设置应用中 配置设置
modify system settings so right settings
修改系统设置以便正确设置
permission okay we're gonna enable that
许可好，我们将启用它
we're gonna trust that this is all good
我们会相信这一切都很好
because sensibo is a legit company and
因为sensibo是一家合法的公司
what do we got here modify system
我们在这里修改了什么系统
settings does it just let me why is it
设置它只是让我为什么是它
taking me to other apps cool ok let's go
带我 去其他应用程序很酷， 我们走吧
back to sensibo do we see it oh there we
回到sensibo我们看到了哦， 我们
go a living room there we go ok so now I
去 客厅那里，我们去 好了 ，所以现在我
don't have an AC unit connected to this
没有连接到此的AC单元
as I'm
因为我
but you can see up at the top right-hand
但你可以在右上方看到
side of the app there do you see that on
应用程序的 身边 还有你看到 ，
your screen at the Left we've got
你 在左边 的 屏幕 我们有
humidity levels we've got a temperature
湿度水平，我们有一个温度
gauge as well and what's neat about
衡量，以及什么是整洁的
sensibo is it allows us to actually
sensibo它实际上允许我们
control our a/c unit not only the on/off
控制我们的 a / c单元 不仅 开/关
state of the air-conditioner if it's got
空调的状态，如果有的话
wireless remote it's going to be able to
无线遥控器 它将能够
control it but it also allows us to
控制它，但它也使我们 能够
control the fan setting and it allows us
控制风扇 设置，它允许我们
to do that from anywhere in the world
从 世界上 任何地方做到这一点
because the app is connecting to the
因为应用程序正在连接到
Internet and the Internet is then
那时互联网和互联网
communicating back with our sensibo
与我们的 sensibo沟通
device and that is is controlled by this
设备， 这是由此控制的
app so cool what does it say ok so
应用程序，以便冷却它说什么了 确定，所以
please observe the indication LED of
请注意指示LED
this device count the number of blanks
此设备计算 空白 的数量
okay
好的
1 1 1 okay in order to complete the
1 1 1没关系 ，以完成
setup ok I did that oh maybe oh that's
设置好我做了哦哦也许哦那是
why it took me here it wants me to turn
为什么它把我带到这里它希望我转向
on oh it needs the right permission okay
哦，它需要 好 正确的权限
it allows the app to read or write
它允许应用程序读取或写入
system settings it needs to read those
它需要阅读那些系统设置
Wi-Fi settings so this is kind of
Wi-Fi 设置，所以这是一种
interesting Sasha because what I'm
有趣的Sasha，因为我是
reading that it's actually doing here
读到它实际上是在这里做的
right is it's making it so I don't have
权利是它使，所以我 没有
to program the sensibo with my Wi-Fi
使用我的Wi-Fi对sensibo进行编程
settings it's going to glean those from
设置它将收集来自
my phone settings so now that I've got
我的手机设置现在已经有了
that set up here let's go back to the
在这里 设置 让我们回到
sensibo app I've turned on the access
sensibo app 我打开了 访问权限
let's see what it does differently
让我们看看它的作用有何不同
could not find sensibo device make sure
找不到sensibo设备确定
your GPS is turned on your phone
您的GPS 已打开手机
location settings oh and I've learned
位置设置哦，我已经学会了
I've lost my miracast
我失去了我的奇迹
sorry oh and just reconnect there for
对不起哦，只是重新连接 那里
you so this is just kind of the initial
你，所以这是正中下怀 最初的
setup that you're gonna go through it is
设置你要经历的是
pretty you know as you see it's pretty
非常你知道，因为你看到它很漂亮
straightforward it's telling me what I
直截了当地告诉我我是什么
need to do let's retry see if it gives
需要 做的 ，让我们再次试 看看它是否给
me a connection this time searching for
我这一次搜索的连接
your sensible device and it looks like
你明智的设备， 它看起来像
it okay to connect your smart AC to the
它好到您的智能AC 连接
Internet
互联网
please select ok so sensibo is now
请选择确定所以现在是sensibo
detecting all the different Wi-Fi
检测所有不同的Wi-Fi
networks and my apparently when it does
网络和我显然是什么时候
that it knocks off miracast so that's
它击败了奇迹，所以那就是
why I lose the connection there I'm
为什么我失去了那里的联系
going to try to bring up the screen here
要 尝试这里弹出屏幕
again for you there we go
我们再去找你
so it's detected all the local Wi-Fi
所以它检测到所有本地Wi-Fi
hotspots I'm going to tell it which one
热点我要告诉它哪一个
is mine and then I need to tell sensible
是我的，然后我需要说明一点
okay what is my password so I'm just
好吧，我的密码是什么， 所以我 只是
going to enter that here mm-hmm I have a
要进入那里mm-hmm 我有一个
really strong password so bear with me
真的很强的密码所以请耐心等待
here folks I have possibly a it's a
在这里伙计 我可能是一个
simple kind of class password 1 2 3 no
简单的类密码1 2 3 没有
how does that connect to your actual
这是如何连接 到 你的实际
Wi-Fi or not you're right the ACAC
无论你是否使用Wi-Fi，ACAC都是对的
that's what's cool so you think about
那就是你想的那么酷
your AC unit that has a wireless remote
您的AC设备配有无线遥控器
control right it's infrared so as I
控制权就像我一样是红外线
control sensibo with my phone with the
用我的手机控制sensibo
app I'm actually triggering a wireless
app我实际上是在触发无线网络
remote control signal infrared from
遥控信号红外线
sensible so okay so then it's it's not
明智的， 所以 没关系，那就 不是了
like sensible is talking to the remote
喜欢明智的是和遥控器说话
that's talking to the AC sensitive
这是与 AC 敏感 的谈话
correct
正确
how could have lost your remote
怎么会丢失你的遥控器
completely since about is the remote
完全是因为关于遥控器
absolutely that's correct
绝对是正确的
ok so it's I got it so that's how it's
好的， 所以我得到了它就是这样的
communicating yeah all right cool ok so
沟通是的， 好吧很酷， 所以
I'm gonna I'm gonna give it a go again
我要去，我要去给它 再次去
here
这里
what kind of blinks have we got one one
什么样的眨眼我们得到了一个
okay maybe I entered my password
好吧也许我输入了 密码
incorrectly let's try again to connect
错误地让我们再次尝试连接
here we go gonna try one last time never
在这里，我们最后一次尝试永远不会
a good idea to talk and type your
说话和输入你的好主意
password at the same time that was all
密码同时是全部
me oh it's me configuring Oh starting AC
我哦，这是我配置哦启动AC
Wi-Fi connection and I've lost miracast
Wi-Fi连接，我失去了奇迹
but I'll fire that back up for you
但我会为你解雇这个问题
there we go waiting for sensibo oh and I
在那里，我们去等待 sensibo哦和我
lost miracast
失去了奇迹
apologies let's bring that back out oh I
道歉让 我 把它带回来 哦我
see what's happening here Sasha it's
看看这里发生了什么Sasha就是这样
connecting direct my phone is connecting
连接直接我的手机正在连接
directly to sensibo it says to use
直接向sensibo说它要使用
miracast disconnect the other Wi-Fi
miracast 断开其他Wi-Fi
direct connection that's why okay so I
直接连接，这就是为什么好吧，所以我
can't really use miracast at the same
不能真正使用 Miracast时 在同一
time that we're doing this so it's
我们正在做的这个时间，所以它的
trying it wants to connect through a
尝试它想通过一个连接
Wi-Fi connection it's almost acting like
Wi-Fi 连接几乎就像
a hotspot so that's kind of cool okay so
一个热点，所以这很酷
now sensibo is connecting to my Wi-Fi
现在sensibo正在连接我的Wi-Fi
network right I can't bring it up on the
网络的权利，我不能把 它 的
screen because as soon as I do I'm
屏幕，因为 我一直这样做
connecting to my Wi-Fi network and then
然后连接到我的Wi-Fi网络
I lose access to the sense of oh that's
我失去了那种感觉哦
interesting so essentially that's all
很有趣， 所以 基本上就是这样
there there is to the setup so you see
那里有设置所以你 看
that this is flash in a way it's it's
这是闪光的一种方式，它是它的
getting the configuration and it's
得到配置，它
connecting to the network this is now
这 是现在连接到 网络
your wireless remote so through your
通过 你的 无线遥控器
through your internet connection through
通过您的互联网连接
the app you're able to control your AC
您可以控制 AC的应用程序
unit alright so then if there are also
单位好吧那么如果还有
like benefits as far as like if you were
类似的好处就好像如果你是
to leave the house like the phone app
像电话应用程序离开房子
doesn't know that you're leaving yeah
不 知道 你要离开 是的
that's what's kind of neat too because
这也是一种整洁， 因为
nest does that nest knows that hey if
那巢是否知道嘿如果
I've left the house as I mentioned it
就像我提到的那样，我已经离开了这所房子
start saving me some energy because it's
开始为我节省一些能量， 因为它是
it knows that I've gone so sensible is
它知道我已经变得如此明智了
the same thing once my app once my phone
一旦我的应用程序一次我的手机同样的事情
is left the Wi-Fi network it knows that
离开了它所知道的Wi-Fi网络
I'm no longer there and it and it acts
我不再在那里， 而且行动起来
accordingly so I can program it to say
因此，我可以编程说
hey let's turn off the AC unit at that
嘿，让我们关掉空调机组在 那
time I feel like they need one of those
一次，我觉得他们需要那些 之一
for my hair streamer I think yeah
对于我的头发流光我觉得是的
definitely as a safety precaution so of
绝对为安全起见 所以
course you know setting up something
当然你知道设置一些东西
like sensibo here
像sensibo这里
on the TV show is a little bit tricky
在电视节目中 有点棘手
and as it goes through the connection
并且当它通过连接
settings and and I'm trying to show it
设置和我试图展示它
on the screen at the same time I've
我 同时在屏幕上
probably monkeyed up a couple things the
大概monkeyed了几个东西
setup itself is very easy breezy as you
设置本身 就像你一样 轻松自如
can see you know the steps are well
可以看到你知道步骤很好
defined in the app it shows you
在它向您显示的应用程序中定义
everything and it's stable and it tends
一切都很稳定 而且趋于 稳定
to work very very well so give it a look
工作非常好， 所以看看
head on over to cap five dot TV slash
转过头来看五点电视 斜线
sensibo and you'll be able to pick one
sensibo，你将能够选择一个
of these up great gift for for under the
对于 下这些了巨大的礼物
tree this year and certainly you know if
树今年， 当然你知道如果
you know somebody who has or if you have
你认识一个拥有或拥有的人
a an AC unit in your window or in the
在 您的窗口或在窗口中的 AC单元
house that is controlled by an infrared
由红外线控制的房子
controller then this is definitely
控制器那么这绝对是
something that will be a benefit to you
对你 有益 的事情
I love that it turns it into a smart
我喜欢 它把它变成 一个聪明的人
device it saves us energy and it makes
它可以为我们节省能源
it so that I can control it from
这样我 就可以控制它 了
anywhere no matter where I am it's
在任何地方，无论我在哪里
perfect there you have it that sense of
在那里完美你 有它的感觉
oh I apologize that I did have you know
哦，我道歉， 我确实让你 知道
I'm waiting on a couple connection
我在等几个连接
things but that's that's what it is on
事情，但那是它的本质
live TV but check it out cat five dot TV
直播电视， 但看看 猫五点电视
slash senseof Oh
斜线感哦
[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[掌声]